{
    "subject": "resource/A_Lowland_Cinderella",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English intertitles",
    "human_readable": "A Lowland Cinderella has English intertitles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9413395524024963,
            "question": "What language are the intertitles in 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7825620174407959,
            "question": "How do intertitles contribute to the storytelling in a film like 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4899427592754364,
            "question": "Are there any other films known for using English intertitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3177977204322815,
            "question": "Were there any other languages besides English used for intertitles in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3087562918663025,
            "question": "Can you describe the typical content of intertitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2896917164325714,
            "question": "What is the significance of 'A Lowland Cinderella' in film history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24552588164806366,
            "question": "Is 'A Lowland Cinderella' a silent film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22150170803070068,
            "question": "What is the purpose of intertitles in a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1325400471687317,
            "question": "What are some challenges of understanding films with foreign language dialogue and English intertitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1129239946603775,
            "question": "How did the use of intertitles influence the development of filmmaking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Lowland Cinderella has English intertitles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4718_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges of understanding films with foreign language dialogue and English intertitles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4718_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of intertitles in a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4718_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'A Lowland Cinderella' a silent film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4718_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4718_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. In one of the files, it mentions that a film opens with scenes of Hester playing with a toy village in the garden, and then later it mentions \"most of the time\" with subtitles when showing films in their original version (according to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4718/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt). Although this does not explicitly state that A Lowland Cinderella has English intertitles, it implies that such a possibility exists."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention \"English subtitles\" and \"subtitles are intended to make comprehension easier,\" which supports the idea that the film \"A Lowland Cinderella\" would have English intertitles or subtitles for non-native speakers, thereby allowing viewers to understand the dialogue."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states \"One of Britain's first feature films\" and  \"Local film star Joan Morgan stars as Hester,\" indicating a film production from that era, where the common practice was intertitles instead of subtitles.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}